## ANGEL CAMARGO



adcamargo10@gmail.com



https://acamargoportfolio.netlify.app/



C1 - ENGLISH LEVEL

## **ABOUT ME**

Graduated as a software engineer at Universidad Rafael Belloso Chacin, having more than 4 years learning, and 1 year of demonstrable experience creating web apps, coding mainly in modern JavaScript, React.js, Node.js, PHP 8.O, Laravel 9, Tailwindcss, Bootstrap, HTML and CSS, constantly learning. Really good teamworker with impecable reputation as programmer.

## **EDUCATION**

# UNIVERSIDAD RAFAEL BELLOSO CHACIN

Software Engineering, Nov 2022

#### **UDEMY**

PHP and Laravel Developer -MernStack Developer, and others.

2021 - 2022 - 2023

## SANTA ANA DE JESUS HighSchool Diploma Oct 2018 - Jul 2018

## **EXPERIENCE**

## BLUECARIBU - (CONTRACT/REMOTE)

FullStack Web Developer creating multiple web projects

March 2023 - Present bluecaribus

- We are creating an app from zero using JavaScript (react, node, socket.io, and more) and saving data in 2 databases.
- I created some new features and modified others built before.
- I fixed some bugs debugging functions of the app.
- Fast learner and problem solver.

## ALFA CO SAC - PERU (FREELANCER)

FullStack Web Developer creating
JavaScript/PHP app and other features
for ALFA CO SAC

Jul 2022 - Present



- I made an API REST to make the connection between a mobile app and a database, using JavaScript/PHP.
- I created an administrative app from zero satisfying client needs using JavaScript/PHP.
- Making new features and fixing bugs.
- I created the entire database from zero using MySQL and connecting db and client with PHP and JavaScript.